复习练习 1-53：弱化音。下面开始例句。
Review exercise 153, reduce sounds. The president hoped to veto the bill. Deposit
it to my account, please. Their boss told them to wait. The coach showed us how to
pitch. Everyone stared at the mess. Stay at my house for a while. Jim looked at his
watch impatiently. He's at his brother's. They said it took too long. Do you think
it turned out? Let's keep it in perspective. We keep it for another day?
This'll do for now. The students all worked for hours. We learned it from the
coach. The tourists came from all over. We made it just in time. The place was in an
uproar. It was an odd remark. He's an open book to me. Everyone sat and chatted for a
while. It was getting later and later. We had two or three options. No one could see
or hear anything. The neighbors are complaining again. Whose shoes are these?
The door's on your left. Are you on your way yet? There's another one later. One of
them is outside. The other one's in here. Did he pass the test? Let's take a cab.
What's the tallest building in America? Do you like a piece of pie? They'll be gone
for a couple of weeks. Do you think you can do it? Can you believe it? We think
he'd never done it before. They'd always done it that way. Why would he tell her? I
don't know if he'd agree. Who was on the phone? The drummer was off beat. Let's see
what he wants. Who knows what it is? Some of it got in my eyes. Somebody took my
place.